<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Country_Profile_Project</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_name">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="pakistan_name">Pakistan</string>
    <string name="turkey_name">Turkey</string>
    <string name="titel_text">Warning</string>
    <string name="message_text">Do you want to exit ?</string>


    <string name="bangladesh_text">

        Bangladesh, to the east of India on the Bay of Bengal, is a South Asian country marked by lush greenery and many waterways. Its Padma (Ganges), Meghna and Jamuna rivers create fertile plains, and travel by boat is common. On the southern coast, the Sundarbans, an enormous mangrove forest shared with Eastern India, is home to the royal Bengal tiger. \n\n
        Capital: Dhaka\n
        CO2 emissions per capita: 0.55 metric tons (2019) \n
        Electricity consumption per capita: 317.25 kWh (2014) \n
        Energy use per capita: 227.13 kg of oil equivalent (2014) \n
        Fertility rate: 2.00 births per woman (2020) \n
        GDP growth rate: 6.9% annual change (2021) \n

    </string>

    <string name="pakistan_text">
        Pakistan emerged on the world map as an independent sovereign state in August 1947, as a result of the division of the British Indian Empire. With a land area of 881,913 sq. km. [including FATA (Federal Administered Tribal Areas) and FANA (Federal Administered Northern Areas)], its population stands at nearly 172.80 million, according to the 2008 Census. Historically, this is one of the most ancient lands known to man. Its cities flourished before Babylon was built; its people practiced the art of good living and citizenship before the celebrated ancient Greeks.\n\n
        President: Arif Alvi Trending\n
        Capital: Islamabad\n
        CO2 emissions per capita: 0.85 metric tons (2019) \n
        Electricity consumption per capita: 419.68 kWh (2014) \n
        Energy use per capita: 431.63 kg of oil equivalent (2014) \n
        Fertility rate: 3.56 births per woman (2020) \n
        GDP growth rate: 6.5% annual change (2021)\n

    </string>

    <string name="turkey_text">
        Turkey, officially the Republic of Türkiye, is a country in Southeast Europe and West Asia. It is mainly on the Anatolian Peninsula in West Asia, with a small portion called East Thrace on the Balkan Peninsula in Southeast Europe.\n\n
        Capital: Ankara\n
        CO2 emissions per capita: 4.75 metric tons (2019)\n
        Electricity consumption per capita: 2,815.04 kWh (2014) \n
        Energy use per capita: 1,628.21 kg of oil equivalent (2015)\n
        Fertility rate: 1.92 births per woman (2020)\n
        GDP growth rate: 11.4% annual change (2021) \n
        Gross domestic product: 819 billion USD (2021) \n

    </string>

</resources>